Do you know how Vietnamese women fish?
without any exaggeration
She fished and found a new ceiling
Not many women in China dare to do this
It's this rural beauty
Not only people are beautiful and graceful
And the fishing technique is also top-notch
The beauty is so domineering just to let us watch him fish.
Came out in pajamas
She said it was very convenient to catch fish this way
I don’t know if it’s inconvenient
But it looks very eye-catching
Next, his fishing skills will definitely make you admire him
I saw him coming to the river and not caring about the turbid water.
I squatted down immediately
They also cleared away the branches and weeds on the shore
My dear
This kind of place is usually a hiding place for bugs and spicy sticks.
The beauty in this place is so courageous
And that's nothing
After he pulled away the weeds
Directly stretched his hand into the mud hole on the shore
Don’t be afraid to touch a tattooed eel
This wave of operations makes my scalp numb
Fortunately there was no accident
Only a piece of tile was found
You see, I also sweated a lot for him
The girl just smiled slightly
Turning around, I reached another position and touched it
Beautiful woman crawls in turbid water
Even if I get soaked, I don’t care
On the contrary, I really enjoy the feeling of skin-to-skin contact.
After a while
I fished out a black fish from the hole
The girl smiled happily
This is a scavenger
This kind of fish is also a good delicacy in the local area.
After harvesting the first fish
The girl is even more excited
I touched it directly in the middle of the river.
Everywhere a girl puts her hands on, he can touch her
No matter how slippery the fish is, it can't escape
In a moment, another scavenger was touched by him.
The girl's fishing skills are really a duck's head.
Frog croaks
And the girl is just warming up
Fishing has just begun
You see, he has touched such a small fish.
The girl said that fishing like this is quite good.
Only those who grew up in rural areas can experience the enjoyment
Not only can it improve food
You can also experience the fun of childhood
While talking, another fish was fished out of the water.
In the blink of an eye, the girl disappeared from our sight
Take a closer look at the camera
It turned out to be buried in the weeds
Although there are many fish in this place,
But there are also a lot of leeches and water bugs
Other girls would be daunted by this
But she doesn't care
After climbing in, I touched it
When I was still worried about girls
A fish was fished out by him
This is still a big guy
Next, the crazy arrest mode started
one piece
two
Sanjo
oh
Four
It only took two hours to harvest less than half a barrel.
enough for a meal
So hardworking and capable
Do you like girls who are not afraid of getting dirty or tired?